<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Zeeshan Chatur</title>
    <link>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Zeeshan Chatur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creator Companion</title>
      <link>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/creatorai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/creatorai/</guid>
      <description>Your browser does not support the video tag. Try the Creator Companion out here. Link to heading Also try out the Accenture AI for the &amp;ldquo;Accenture AI Leaders Podcast&amp;rdquo; here. Link to heading Code for this project. Link to heading Introduction: Link to heading Podcasts offer a wealth of information and entertainment, but navigating through extensive libraries of episodes to find specific content can be challenging. That&amp;rsquo;s where the Creator Companion app comes in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Episodes</title>
      <link>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/podcastep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/podcastep/</guid>
      <description> Here is a list of some of my favorite Podcast Episodes (in no particular order): Link to heading #1. reCAPTCHA and Duolingo: Luis von Ahn Link to heading #2. Lord of the Rankings Link to heading </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/books/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my favorite books I have read (mostly listend to): Link to heading 1. Outliers by Malcolm Gladwell Link to heading Outliers by Malcolm Gladwell is a really interesting book that shows how success isn&amp;rsquo;t just about being really talented or working really hard - it&amp;rsquo;s also about having the right opportunities and circumstances.
2. The Creative Act: A Way of Being by Rick Rubin Link to heading The Creative Act by Rick Rubin is an inspiring essay that offers valuable insights into the creative process, emphasizing the importance of authenticity, collaboration, and experimentation in unlocking one&amp;rsquo;s creative potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Byte: Pizza Review Analysis</title>
      <link>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/onebyte/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.zeeshanchatur.com/posts/onebyte/</guid>
      <description>Here is the Code for this project. Link to heading Table of Contents Link to heading 1. Intro Link to heading 2. Data Link to heading 3. Consistency Link to heading 4. Scores Link to heading 5. Location Link to heading 6, Youtube Analytics Link to heading 7. Rankings Link to heading Intro Link to heading Welcome To One Byte: a visual data analysis project that analyzes the data from Dave Portnoy’s One Bite Pizza series.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
