<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zeeshan Chatur</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zeeshan Chatur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Episodes</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/posts/podcastep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/posts/podcastep/</guid>
      <description> Here is a list of some of my favorite Podcast Episodes (in no particular order): Link to heading #1. reCAPTCHA and Duolingo: Luis von Ahn Link to heading #2. Lord of the Rankings Link to heading </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/posts/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/posts/books/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my favorite books I have read (mostly listend to): Link to heading 1. Outliers by Malcolm Gladwell Link to heading Outliers by Malcolm Gladwell is a really interesting book that shows how success isn&amp;rsquo;t just about being really talented or working really hard - it&amp;rsquo;s also about having the right opportunities and circumstances.
2. The Creative Act: A Way of Being by Rick Rubin Link to heading The Creative Act by Rick Rubin is an inspiring essay that offers valuable insights into the creative process, emphasizing the importance of authenticity, collaboration, and experimentation in unlocking one&amp;rsquo;s creative potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>temas</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/categoria/temas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:21:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/categoria/temas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sintaxe</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/categoria/sintaxe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:21:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/categoria/sintaxe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Códigos curtos</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/tags/shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:51:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/tags/shortcodes/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, My name is Zeeshan Chatur and I am from Dallas, Texas. I am currently a student at Texas A&amp;amp;M University majoring in Management Information Systems.
I am passionate about data analytics, machine learning and AI. I am always on the lookout for new things and advancements in these areas. Data is one of the things I love and I am driven by the desire to uncover insights, patterns and trends that can help understand the world better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to contact me at: zeeshanchatur@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>One Byte: Pizza Review Analysis Link to heading Welcome to One Byte, a data analysis project that analyzes the data from Dave Portnoy&amp;rsquo;s One Bite Pizza series. The One Bite Pizza reviews started in 2014 and have really gained popularity since 2016, with a new review being uploaded almost daily since then. As a fan of pizza, I have always been searching for the perfect slice. That&amp;rsquo;s why I have analyzed over 1300 pizza locations reviewed by Dave Portnoy in his One Bite Pizza series to bring you the ultimate guide to finding the best pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
